Darshit Savaliya

Web Designer



+91 97374 36065 darshit97374@gmail.com

D-2, 103 Opera Palm, Kholvad Road, Pasodara patiya, Surat, Gujarat-394190.

PROFILE

I have a 2+ Year up experience as a web designer and am proficient in HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap. I have designed and developed websites that are user-friendly, responsive, and visually appealing. My strong knowledge of HTML, CSS and Bootstrap has allowed me to create custom designs that cater to the specific needs of clients.

EXPERIENCE

Web Designer - 01/11/2022 to Currently Working Ethnic Infotech / Surat, Gujarat.

Ethnic Infotech is an E-commerce company that offers a seamless online shopping experience with a wide range of products, combining convenience, reliability, and exceptional customer service.

Web Designer - 01/02/2022 to 31/11/2022 HHG Softech Private Limited / Surat, Gujarat.

HHG Softech Private Limited's Worker System website provides an efficient platform for managing workforce operations, optimizing productivity, and streamlining communication, empowering businesses with effective workforce management solutions.

Web Designer - 01/08/2021 to 31/01/2022

Renowiz Technologies and Solutions Pvt Ltd / Surat, Gujarat.

Renowiz Technologies and Solutions Pvt Ltd's Product Besa website offers a user-friendly interface for browsing and purchasing a wide range of products, providing a seamless online shopping experience with secure transactions and timely deliveries.



EDUCATION

2019 - 2022

Bachelors's in Computer

Application

Jaipur National University

2017 - 2018 H.S.C G.N. damani high school-Dhari

2015 - 2016 S.S.C Jivan Dhara School-Dhari

LANGUAGE

- Gujarati
- Hindi
- English

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Media Query
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- XD